Rear doors · clear opening
Open left door
Open right door
Close left door
Close right door
Bed buckle · continuous belt connection and reinsertion
Press red button · release tongue and belt
Insert metal tongue · refasten belt
ECG net · fixed suspension and lower release
Press aisle buckle · lower corner drops; upper support stays
Press wall buckle · lower net folds; supports stay
Insert wall tongue
Insert aisle tongue · net secured
Cargo net · fixed wall attachment and supply retrieval
Press red button · release net; fixed ties stay
Fetch wipe canister
Return supplies
Reconnect receiver to fixed tongue · secure net
Handset · firmer cable and replacement
Pick up handset
Return handset · cable settles
Power plug · unplug, hold and reconnect
Withdraw power plug
Hold disconnected plug
Release plug · restrained cable drop
Reconnect to socket